[
  {
    "question": "Aqua?",
    "answers": ["useless", "garbage", "trash"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the object that opposing players must destroy in order to win at \"League of Legends\"?",
    "answers": ["nexus"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the average amount of time a player of \"Fortnite\" spends enjoying the game weekly?",
    "answers": ["6 hours", "10 hours", "7 hours", "8 hours", "9 hours", "6-10 hours"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the woman Mario is attempting to save from the giant ape in the original Donkey Kong?",
    "answers": ["pauline"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The original street design for Liberty City in \"Grand Theft Auto\" was based on which real-life metropolis?",
    "answers": ["New York City"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the name of the cartoon-like interludes that interrupt videogame play to narrate the story?",
    "answers": ["cutscenes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A pickaxe is a basic, commonly-used tool in which videogame?",
    "answers": ["minecraft"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the racing series that is a spinoff of \"Super Mario Brothers\"?",
    "answers": ["mario kart", "mario-kart"]
  },
  {
    "question": "The classic arcade game \"Pong\" was manufactured by which company?",
    "answers": ["atari"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What are the professions of Mario and his brother Luigi?",
    "answers": ["plumbers"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What does Mario jump on when he completes a level?",
    "answers": ["a flag pole", "a pole", "a flag", "flag", "pole", "flag pole"]
  },
  {
    "question": "How many players can compete against each other simultaneously in a \"Fortnite Battle Royale\"?",
    "answers": ["100", "hundred", "one-hundred"]
  },
  {
    "question": "SK Telecom T1 are accomplished eGamers associated with which game?",
    "answers": ["league of legends", "league"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the name of the final course in all \"Mario Kart\" videogames?",
    "answers": ["rainbow road", "rainbow"]
  },
  {
    "questions": "Which item made Mario invincible in \"Super Mario Bros.\"?",
    "answers": ["starman", "star"]
  },
  {
    "questions": "What is the name of the circular object that is used to collect Pokémon?",
    "answers": ["pokeball", "poke-ball", "poke ball"]
  },
  {
    "questions": "\"Notch\" is the world-famous designer of which videogame?",
    "answers": ["Minecraft"]
  },
  {
    "questions": "The word \"Pokémon\" is generally understood to be a translation of which phrase?",
    "answers": ["poket monsters", "poket monster", "poket-monsters", "poket-monster"]
  },
  {
    "questions": "IDK this halt",
    "answers": "yes"
  }
]
